Guide to the Stefan Brecht Papers MSS.355
Fales Library and Special Collections
Stefan Brecht Papers
1960-2000
1960-1980
Fales Library and Special Collections
Brecht, Stefan, 1924-2009
MSS.355
20 Linear Feet (30 boxes)
The Stefan Brecht Papers documents writer, critic, and performer Stefan Brecht's critical analysis of and participation in a wide range of experimental theater and performance productions. The collection consists of research files compiled and created by Brecht in the course of working on his (mostly unpublished) series of books "The Original Theatre of New York: From the Mid-Sixties to the Mid-Seventies." The collection comprises playbills, plays, original artworks, posters, invitations, notes, photographs, media, newspaper clippings, correspondence, articles, books, interviews and other book research material.
Provenance
The Stefan Brecht papers were donated to NYU Libraries by Brecht's wife Rena Gill in 2012.
Conditions Governing Access
Materials are open to researchers. Please contact the Fales Library and Special Collections, fales.library@nyu.edu, 212-998-2596.
Biographical Note
Stefan Brecht was born November 3, 1924 in Berlin to playwright Bertolt Brecht and actress Helene Weigel. The family lived briefly in Finland, Stockholm, and Denmark before arriving in Santa Monica, California in 1941. Although the rest of the family left America after Bertolt Brecht was interrogated by HUAC, Stefan Brecht stayed to finish his M.A. thesis on Hegel at UCLA. He then earned a PhD in philosophy from Harvard, and went on to teach and study in Miami and Paris.
Brecht later came to New York City, where he lived in the Chelsea Hotel and became very involved in the experimental theater and performance collectives emerging in the late sixties. He wrote about downtown New York avant-garde performers with the intention of creating a nine-book opus with the overarching title "The Original Theatre of New York: From the Mid-Sixties to the Mid-Seventies." He completed three books: "Queer Theatre;" "The Theatre of Visions: Robert Wilson;" and the two volume "Peter Schumann's Bread and Puppet Theatre." In addition to writing about the theater world, Stefan Brecht befriended and supported many playwrights and theater collectives; he also participated in productions as a performer. Although Brecht additionally published many articles and two books of poems, a large portion of his writing remains unpublished. Brecht died on April 13, 2009.
Sources:
GILL, RENA. "STEFAN BRECHT, 1924-2009." Communications from the International Brecht Society 2009: 24+. International Bibliography of Theatre & Dance with Full Text. Web. 20 Sept. 2013.
Weber, Bruce. "Brecht the younger chronicled the avant-garde." Globe & Mail [Toronto, Canada] 27 Apr. 2009: S10. Biography In Context. Web. 20 Aug. 2013
Arrangement
The Stefan Brecht Papers are arranged into eight series, with additional oversize series for series I-V listed at the end of the finding aid. The series reflect the original order of the material upon arrival, and all of Brecht's original file labelling has been retained. Series I is arranged alphabetically by subject's last name while all other series are by production name.
The Series are as follows:
Series I: Performance Overview Subject Files A-Z
Series II: Stuart Sherman
Series III: Mabou Mines
Series IV: Performance Group "Wooster Group"
Series V: Dance, Black Theatre, Black Music
Series VI: Sound recordings
Series VII: Video recordings
Series VIII: Films
Related Materials
Mabou Mines Archive (MSS.133)
Stuart Sherman Papers (MSS.192)
Richard Foreman Papers (MSS.152)
Jaime Davidovich Papers (MSS.155)
Scope and Content
The Stefan Brecht Papers documents Brecht's critical analysis of and participation in a wide range of experimental theater and performance productions. The collection consists of research material compiled and created by Brecht for his proposed nine book series: "The Original Theatre of the City of New York, From the Mid-Sixties to the Mid-Seventies." Three books of the nine were published: "Queer Theatre"; "The Theatre of Visions: Robert Wilson"; and the two-volume "Peter Schumann's Bread and Puppet Theatre." Although there is significant crossover between unpublished and published subjects, the collection is stronger in unpublished material. As Rena Gill describes in her memoriam article "Stefan Brecht 1924-2009," the following subjects were additionally planned for inclusion as elements of the overarching book project: Richard Foreman's Diary Theatre: Theatre as Personal Phenomenology of Mind; Theatre as Psychotherapy for Performers: Joseph Chaikin's Open Theatre and The Beck's Living Theatre; Richard Schechner's Performance Group with Andre Gregory's Manhattan Repertory Company and With Notes on Grotowski and Andre Serban; The 1970's Hermetic Theatre of the Performing Director: Jared Bark, Stuart Sherman, John Zorn, Melvin Andringa with appendices on Ann Wilson, Robert Whitman and Wilford Leach; Theatre as Collective Improvisation: The Mabou Mines; Black Theatre and Music with notes on the Duo Theatre and Melvin van Peebles; and Dance: Merce Cunningham, Yvonne Rainer, Meredith Monk, Douglans Dunn with a note on Ping Chong.
The collection comprises playbills, plays, original artworks, posters, invitations, notes, ephemera, photographs, media, newspaper clippings, correspondence, articles, books, interviews and other book research material. Brecht was fastidious in his collecting and descriptive practices, as evidenced by his detailed notes, correspondence requesting diverse research material and original plays, and clippings from multiple sources across a variety of subjects. Frequently Brecht's notes and sketches can be found in the margins of flyers, clippings, and invitations. Each newspaper clipping has been photocopied for preservation purposes. All title headings have been retained from the original folders. The bulk of material is from 1965-1985 and was compiled in New York City.
The Papers are comprised of eight series:
Series I: Performance Overview Subject Files A-Z
This series is comprised of research files Brecht compiled in the course of his research for his nine book series "The Original Theatre of the City of New York, From the Mid-Sixties to the Mid-Seventies." Subject files are organized alphabetically by last name of subject. This series contains considerable overlap with the rest of the collection and may have been a place where Brecht kept more general, or overarching files. Each subject file contains a combination of newspaper clippings, notes, and ephemera. Subject files contain both handwritten notes and annotated typescripts. There is a wide range of depth with which each subject is covered. Folders labeled 'preface' or 'overview' do not necessarily contain Brecht's writing, but rather research material Brecht may have been considering using in his prefaces or overviews, alongside fragments of writing or preliminary drafts. Material ranges from 1960-2000, with a majority from 1975-1985.
Series II: Stuart Sherman
This series includes files that Brecht compiled while he was researching his book on artist Stuart Sherman. The files contain original artworks, including drawings and poetry pieces, which are often accompanied by correspondence. Correspondence includes both personal greetings and contributions towards Brecht's research. The series contains photographs documenting Sherman's "Spectacles," copies of Stuart Sherman's The Quotidian Review, and newspaper clippings. There are two sets of interview transcripts, one conducted by Stefan Brecht and another by John Matturri. Included are Stefan Brecht's notes documenting Stuart Sherman events and personal interactions. Material ranges from the early 1970s to the late 1990s. Most material was produced in New York City, with a small amount from Stuart Sherman's time living in Germany. Interview transcripts can be found of correlating audio material.
Series III: Mabou Mines
This series comprises files that Brecht compiled while he was working on his unfinished book on the avant-garde theater company Mabou Mines. Files consist of notes, newspaper clippings, original scripts, correspondence, and ephemera including posters, tickets, and invitations organized by specific production. Correspondence includes both personal greetings, solicitations for support, and contributions towards Brecht's research. The series starts with selections from the Performing Arts Services Files, each containing photographs with a one page description. Material ranges from early 1970s to early 2000s.
Series IV: Performance Group "Wooster Group"
This series comprises files compiled by Brecht in the course of his research for his unfinished book on the Performance Group, Wooster Group. The research documents the Performance Group under the direction of Richard Schechner as well as its evolution into The Wooster Group with the works of Spalding Grey, Elizabeth LaCompte, and others. The series includes interviews with Richard Schechner and Joan MacIntosh. Research files on the Living Theater and Open Theater are included in this series; Brecht may have been making an intended connection between them. The series contains notes, newspaper clippings, original scripts, correspondence, and ephemera including posters, tickets, and invitations organized by production. Material ranges from 1960s to 2000s. Interview transcripts can be found of correlating audio material.
Series V: Dance, Black Theater, Black Music
This series includes files compiled by Brecht during research for his unfinished books on dance, black theater and black music. Although Brecht may have envisioned this as two separate books within the larger opus, the material is slightly interwoven. The series consists of notes, newspaper clippings, correspondence, and ephemera including posters, tickets, and invitations. Material ranges from 1960-1979 with a significant portion of undated material.
Series VI: Sound recordings
This series contains audiocassettes, audio reels, and a 12" vinyl sound disc. All audio material contains corresponding transcripts that can be found by searching for transcripts specifically or by their similar titles.
Series VII: Video recordings
This series contains six videotapes. All titles should reflect where the videos were removed from, except for "Olga's House of Shame," which was separated from Series IV: Performance Group "Wooster Group"
Series VIII: Films
This series contains four films, all originally housed in Series II: Stuart Sherman.
Oversize Series I-V
Oversize materials largely consist of posters and event programs. Unless otherwise noted, all titles reflect where in the collection material was separated from.
Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
Audiovisual materials have not been preserved and may not be available to researchers.
Experimental theater; Scripts (documents); Performance art -- New York (State) -- New York -- Exhibitions.; Photographs.; Manuscripts; Experimental theater -- 20th century; Art criticism.; Puppet theater.; Avant-garde (Music); Poetry.; Plays (performed works); Interviews.; Monk, Meredith; Rainer, Yvonne, 1934-; Chaikin, Joseph, 1935-; Chong, Ping; Merce Cunningham Dance Company; Gregory, André; LeCompte, Elizabeth; Zorn, John, 1953-; Foreman, Richard; Living Theatre (New York, N.Y.); Leach, Wilford, 1929-1988; Breuer, Lee; Schechner, Richard; MacIntosh, Joan; Beck, Julian, 1925-1985; Beckett, Samuel, 1906-1989; Gray, Spalding, 1941-2004; Shepard, Sam, 1943-2017; Wilson, Ann, 1931-; Malina, Judith, 1926-; Akalaitis, JoAnne; Andringa, Mel; Mabou Mines (Theater group); Sherman, Stuart, 1945-2001; Maleczech, Ruth
- Series I: Performance Overview Subject Files A-Z
  Scope and Content
  This series comprises research files that were compiled by Brecht in the course of his research for his nine book series "The Original Theatre of the City of New York, From the Mid-Sixties to the Mid-Seventies." Subject files are organized alphabetically by last name of subject. This series contains considerable overlap with the rest of the collection and may have been a place where Brecht kept more general, or overarching files. Each subject file contains a combination of newspaper clippings, notes, and ephemera. Subject Files contain both handwritten notes and annotated typescripts. There is a wide range of depth with which each subject is covered. Folders labeled 'preface' or 'overview' do not necessarily contain Brecht's writing, but rather research material Brecht may have been considering using in his prefaces or overviews, alongside fragments of writing or preliminary drafts. Material ranges from 1960-2000, with a majority from 1975-1985.
  - Avant-Gard Theatre- Trends, [1987] (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - "Miscellaneous"- [New York Times article about Jonas Mekas], December 9, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - "Preface", [undated] (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Lydenberg/Arsen- "Alternative Theatre" Nixon Play, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Overview- "The Politics, Packaging, and Potential of Performance Art" R.G. Davis, February, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Overview- [Clippings 1 of 2], [undated] (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Overview- [Clippings 2 of 2], [undated] (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Overview- [1 of 3][articles and press releases including Other Stages vol. 1 no. 10], [undated] (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Overview- [2 of 3][press releases and BAM press], [undated] (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Overview- [3 of 3][articles and press releases, playbill for "Pilobolus"], [undated] (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Andringa, Mel- New Theater Building and Grant Application, September, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Andringa, Mel- Drawing Legion Financial Report, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Andringa, Mel- The Drawing Legion Presents, [1983-1985] (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Andringa, Mel- "At Linda Russman's 19th Street West Theatre", March 26, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Andringa, Mel- "The Fall of Babylon", February, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Andringa, Mel- Legionnaire 10th Anniversary Issue, December, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Andringa, Mel- The Years at Biograph- "The Fall of Babylon", [1984] (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Andringa, Mel- "Mickery Dossier 8" Belshazzar's Feast: description by Mel Andriga, presented by Thomas T. Spears, January, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Andringa, Mel- "Puzzle Pictures" and "Babylon", [undated] (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Andringa, Mel- Drawing Legion [Board Minutes, Financial Summary], 1980-1984 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Andringa, Mel- "Robinson Caruso on Mars", [1983] (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Andringa, Mel- "Legionnaire; Irregular Newsletter from the Drawing Legion", [1981-1983] (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Andringa, Mel- [Correspondence], 1981, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Andringa, Mel- "Camillo/Heptaplus", [1980-1982] (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Andringa, Mel- "Winston Churchill in America", [undated] (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Andringa, Mel- "The Collected Poems of Sir Winston Churchill" by F. John Herbert, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Andringa, Mel- "Belshazzar's Feast", [1979] (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Andringa, Mel- "Belshazzar's Feast"- [Photographs], July, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Andringa, Mel- "Belshazzar's Feast" June 1979 Production (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Andringa, Mel- "Belshazzar's Feast" July 1979 Production (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Andringa, Mel- "The Performer has gotten a performance together...", [undated] (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Andringa, Mel- "The Last Supper" [Photos, notes, reciept of donation], March-April, 1979 (Box 2, Drawer 15)
  - Andringa, Mel- "Eight Preliminary Paintings and A First Reading For Camillo", [undated] (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Andringa, Mel- "Babylon/34th Street" at Artists Space, December, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Andringa, Mel- "Belshazzar's Feast" [A thesis submitted for the University of Iowa MFA], May, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Andringa, Mel- "Belshazzar's Feast" [Photographs], July, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Andringa, Mel- [Brecht's writing], January 4, 1975; March 3, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Andringa, Mel- "Sistine Floor Plan" and "American Nervousness", [undated] (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Andringa, Mel- "The Confidence Man" [1 of 9], [1975-1977] (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Andringa, Mel- "The Confidence Man" [Reciepts] [2 of 9], [Circa 1977] (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Andringa, Mel- "The Confidence Man" [Correspondence and Reciepts] [3 of 9], [1976-1977, undated] (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Andringa, Mel- "The Confidence Man" Mel's Fordham Show [Photographs] [4 of 9], [undated] (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Andringa, Mel- "The Confidence Man" [Photographs] [5 of 9], [undated] (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Andringa, Mel- "The Confidence Man" [6 of 9], [1975-1976] (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Andringa, Mel- "The Confidence Man" [And Jacob's Dream] [7 of 9], [1975-1976] (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Andringa, Mel- "The Confidence Man" [8 of 9], [1975-1976] (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Andringa, Mel- "The Confidence Man" [Jigsaw Puzzle Lecture][9 of 9], March, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Andringa, Mel- "The Sistine Floor Plan", [undated] (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Andringa, Mel- Interview [Transcript about "The Last Supper"], April 17, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Andringa, Mel- Interview on his time with Richard Foreman "First on his recent trip to Iowa; then on Foreman's 'Hotel China'"[Transcript], May 17, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Andringa, Mel- "The Last Supper" [Bound original artwork], [undated] (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Andringa, Mel- Drawing Legion [and CSPS] [1 of 7], 1996-2002 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Andringa, Mel- Drawing Legion [Art over AIDS] [2 of 7], [1991-1992] (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Andringa, Mel- "Tractor: a quarterly magazine of Iowa arts and culture" [3 of 7], [1994-1995] (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Andringa, Mel- "Tractor: a quarterly magazine of Iowa arts and culture" [4 of 7], 1993 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Andringa, Mel- Drawing Legion [publications and events] [5 of 7], [1992-1993] (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Andringa, Mel- Drawing Legion [Correspondence and Solicitations] [6 of 7], [1992-1993] (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Andringa, Mel- ["American Nervousness"] [7 of 7], [1988-1990] (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Anton, Rob, 1978-1984 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Artaud- Jerry Mayer's "TAUD Show", 1978 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Bark, Jared, [1975-1976] (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Beckett, Samuel, [1956-1993] (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Berkoff, Steven, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Bernard, Kenneth, [1985-1992] (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Brakhage, Stan, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Brooks, Peter, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Brown, Beverly, circa 1980 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Brown, Trisha, [undated] (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Burton, Scott, [1975-1976] (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Cage, John, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Cement Action/ G. Ference, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Chaikin, Joseph- [1 of 5], [undated] (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Chaikin, Joseph- [2 of 5], [1980-1981] (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Chaikin, Joseph- [3 of 5], [1978-1980] (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Chaikin, Joseph-"Seagull" [4 of 5], 1975 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Chaikin, Joseph- [5 of 5], circa 1975 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Childs, Lucinda, [1976-1988] (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Chong, Ping- ["Alice", "Arace", Fiji Company][1 of 6], [circa 1982-1984] (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Chong, Ping- ["Rainer and the Knife", Guggenheim Fellowship][2 of 6], [circa 1981-1982] (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Chong, Ping- ["A.M./A.M.", "Nuit Blanche"][3 of 6], [1981-1989] (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Chong, Ping- ["Nuit Blanche", "Fear and Loathing in Gotham"] [4 of 6], circa 1981 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Chong, Ping- ["Humboldt's Current", "Fear and Loathing in Gotham", "Lazarus"][5 of 6], circa 1978 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Chong, Ping- ["Fear and Loathing in Gotham", "Humboldt's Current"][6 of 6], circa 1975 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Clarke, Martha- Music Theater Group, April 17, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Creation [Production Company]`, [undated] (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Cricot 2 Theater- T. Kantor (Polish), 1979-1985 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Cunningham, Merce- See also New American Theatre [1 of 2], [1971-1983] (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Cunningham, Merce- See also New American Theatre [2 of 2], 1975-1976 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Davidovich, Jaime-(Video), 1976 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Dunn, Douglas- [1 of 2], [1975-1979] (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Dunn, Douglas- [2 of 2], [1975-1979] (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Dunn, Joe-American Contemporary Theatre (Buffalo), 1977-1978 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Duo Theatre- Spanish Theatre, circa 1975 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Evans, Joan, [1977-1989] (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Finley, Karen, [1986-1988] (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Gehr, Ernie- See also Richard Foreman, 1983, [undated] (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Gelber, Jack- and Barbara Shore, [1974-1976] (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Gibson, Jon [see also S. Reich], 1988 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Gordon, David- and Valda Setterfield, [1979-1982, undated] (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Gordon, Peter, January 11, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Gourfain, Peter, May 25, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Grand Union, 1975-1976 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Gregory, Andre- "Seagull", "Manhattan Reperatory", "Our Late Night", [1973-1977] (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Grooms, Red, [1973-1975, undated] (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Grotowski, Jerry- See also New American Theatre, [1986, 1999, undated] (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Hatanaka, Minoru, [1979, undated] (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Hill, Robert Nemo, April 6, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Hirsch, Shelley, April 4, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Hoberman, Jim- See also Stuart Sherman, 1975-1976 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Indiana, Gary, [undated] (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Ionesco, Eugene- [articles], [1959-1960] (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Jacobs, Ken, December 1974 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Jesurun, John- [1 of 4], [1985-1987] (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Jesurun, John- "Black Maria" annotated typescript [2 of 4], [undated] (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Jesurun, John- [3 of 4], circa 1988 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Jesurun, John- [4 of 4], [circa 1991-1997] (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Jones, Leroi- See also New American Theatre (Amiri Baraka) [1 of 7], [Circa 1979-1984] (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Jones, Leroi- See also New American Theatre (Amiri Baraka: "What was the relationship of the lone ranger to the means of production?") [2 of 7], [1978-1979] (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Jones, Leroi- See also New American Theatre (Amiri Baraka: "Images of Struggle and Revolution") [3 of 7], 1978 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Jones, Leroi- See also New American Theatre (Amiri Baraka): "The Motion of History" and "S-1", [1976] (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Jones, Leroi- See also New American Theatre (Amiri Baraka: "S-1") [5 of 7], 1976 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Jones, Leroi- See also New American Theatre (Amiri Baraka: "Hard Facts" excerpts) [6 of 7], 1973-1975 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Jones, Leroi- See also New American Theatre (Amiri Baraka: "S-1" and "Sidnee Poet Heroical") [7 of 7], [undated, 1974-1975] (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Katz, Leandro, [1979-1992] (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Katz, Leandro- "Mirror in the Moon", [1984] (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Katz, Leandro-"Mirror on the Moon" [and "The Milk of Amnesia"], [1985] (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Katz, Leandro- "Mirror in the Moon" [Mexico], Circa 1985 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Katz, Leandro- "Mirror in the Moon" Yucatan Sequence [annotated typescript], [undated] (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Katz, Leandro- "Mirror on the Moon", [1983-1985] (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Kelman, Ken, [undated] (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - King, Kenneth, Circa 1981 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - King Trilogy-"Other Stages", June 16, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Kongress, [Crozier], [undated] (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Kushner, Tony, [Circa 1993-1994] (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Leach, Wilford- C.O.R.F.A.X. [1 of 3], 1975-1976 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Leach, Wilford- C.O.R.F.A.X. [typescript][2 of 3], 1975-1976 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Leach, Wilford- C.O.R.F.A.X. [3 of 3], 1975-1976 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Leach, Wilford- [1 of 4], 1975-1977 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Leach, Wilford- ["Carmilla"] [2 of 4], 1975-1977 (Box 7, Folder 2)